Finding aid to the Classes of 1911-1920 records CA.MS.01018
Smith College Archives
- Class of 1914 Records, 1910-1985; 24.042 linear feet (38 containers)
  - Reunions, 1959 (Box 1850, Folder 4)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1914 (Box 1848, Folder 3)
  - Senior Dramatics-Correspondence, 1914 (Box 1848, Folder 4)
  - Senior Dramatics-Photographs, 1914 (Box 1848, Folder 5)
  - Senior Dramatics-Photographs, 1914 (Box 1848, Folder 6)
  - Songs, undated (Box 1848, Folder 7)
  - Sophomore Reception to 1915, 1911 (Box 1848, Folder 8)
  - Step Sings, 1914 (Box 1848, Folder 9)
  - Class Supper, 1914 (Box 1848, Folder 10)
  - Treasurer's File, 1979-1983 (Box 1848, Folder 11)
  - Vespers Service, 1914 (Box 1848, Folder 12)
  - Individuals A-Bee (Box 1851)
  - Individuals Bel-Bu (Box 1852)
  - Individuals C-G (Box 1852.1)
  - Individuals H-L (Box 1853)
  - Individuals M-Ra (Box 1854)
  - Individuals Re-Spa (Box 1855)
  - Individuals Spe-Z (Box 1856)
  - Case, Elizabeth Browning (memorabilia book) (Box 1869.1)
  - Choate, Helen Raymond (memorabilia book) (Box 1869.2)
  - Coulton, Mildred Louise (memorabilia book) (Box 1857)
  - Coulton, Mildred Louise (class notes) (Box 1858)
  - Coulton, Mildred Louise (class notes) (Box 1859)
  - Cutter, Esther (memorabilia book) (Box 1869.3)
  - Darrow, Alice Chamberlain (musical programs, scrapbook) (Box 1869.4)
  - Ellinwood, Cornelia (photo album) (Box 1869.9)
  - Hill, Ruth Beatrice Taylor (scrapbook) (Box 1869.5)
  - Hixon, Blanche Virginia (correspondence) (Box 1861)
  - Hixson, Blanche Virginia (memorabilia book) (Box 1869.6)
  - Hooper, Frances Milliken (correspondence, photographs) (Box 1860)
  - Hooper, Frances Milliken (photo album) (Box 1869.6)
  - Loth, Sara E. (scrapbook) (Box 1861.1)
  - Munroe, Hazel Josephine (photo album) (Box 1869.9)
  - Ochtman, Dorothy (photo album) (Box 1862)
  - Patten, Grace Edith (correspondence, class work) (Box 1862)
  - Patten, Grace Edith (memorabilia book) (Box 1862.1)
  - Reed, Gwendolen Willitts (memorabilia book) (Box 1863)
  - Remington, Agnes (photo album) (Box 1869.7)
  - Stanley, Myrrl Virginia (memorabilia book) (Box 1869.8)
  - Tolman, Mary Heywood (memorabilia book) (Box 1864)
  - Tomlinson, Ruth (post grad correspondence) (Box 1865)
  - Tomlinson, Ruth (family photo album) (Box 1866)
  - Tomlinson, Ruth (travel notes,) (Box 1867)
  - Tomlinson, Ruth (travel notes,) (Box 1868)
  - Weil, Janet (Box 1869.1)
  - Willard, Mary Gerrish (photograph album) (Box 1869)
  - Yereance, Jeannie Quinn (memorabilia book) (Box 1869)
  - Photograph (Box 1847.1)
- Class of 1915 Records, 1911-1985; 11.167 linear feet (17 containers)
  The Class of 1915 was the thirty-sixth entering class and the thirty-sixth graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1915 records, 1911-1985, contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1915, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, programs, Secretary's notes, Treasurer's notes, and other memorabilia.
  - General, 1914; 1982; undated (Box 1870, Folder 1)
  - Baccalaureate, 1915 (Box 1870, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, 1915-1916; 1940 (Box 1870, Folder 3)
  - Collation, 1915 (Box 1870, Folder 4)
  - Commencement, 1915 (Box 1870, Folder 5)
  - Commencement Music, 1915 (Box 1870, Folder 6)
  - Commencement Photographs, 1915 (Box 1870, Folder 7)
  - Freshman Grind by 1914, 1911 (Box 1870, Folder 8)
  - Groups, 1911-1915 (Box 1870, Folder 9)
  - Hoop Rolling, 1915 (Box 1870, Folder 10)
  - Ivy Day, 1915 (Box 1870, Folder 11)
  - Ivy Day Photographs, 1915 (Box 1870, Folder 12)
  - Junior Ushers, 1914 (Box 1870, Folder 13)
  - Junior Prom, 1914 (Box 1870, Folder 14)
  - Junior Prom-Garden Party, 1914 (Box 1870, Folder 15)
  - Last Chapel, 1915 (Box 1870, Folder 16)
  - Last Sing, 1915 (Box 1870, Folder 17)
  - Class Letters, 1924-1985 (Box 1870, Folder 18)
  - Loan Forms for Paintings from Museum of Art, 1969 (Box 1870, Folder 19)
  - Reunions, 1916 (Box 1871, Folder 1)
  - Reunions, 1925-1928 (Box 1871, Folder 2)
  - Reunions, 1930 (Box 1871, Folder 3)
  - Reunions, 1935 (Box 1871, Folder 4)
  - Reunions, 1940 (Box 1871, Folder 5)
  - Reunions, 1940 (Box 1871, Folder 6)
  - Reunions, 1950-1955 (Box 1871, Folder 7)
  - Reunions, 1960-1965 (Box 1871, Folder 8)
  - Reunions, 1970 (Box 1871, Folder 9)
  - Reunions, 1975 (Box 1871, Folder 12)
  - Reunions: Correspondence, 1975 (Box 1871, Folder 10)
  - Reunions: Material Collected by Marian Palmer Faulkner, 1975 (Box 1871, Folder 11)
  - Reunions, 1980-1986 (Box 1871, Folder 13)
  - Reunion Songs, undated (Box 1871, Folder 14)
  - Reunions-Costume and Banner (Box 1874.1)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-A-Behrens (Box 1873, Folder 1)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Bell-Bradt (Box 1873, Folder 2)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Breckenridge-Buttler (Box 1873, Folder 3)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Carpenter-Collins (Box 1873, Folder 4)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Cooke-Damon (Box 1873, Folder 5)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Deney-Egbert (Box 1873, Folder 6)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Evans-Frey (Box 1873, Folder 7)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Friel-Gibbons (Box 1874, Folder 1)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Gibling-Griffith (Box 1874, Folder 2)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Hills-Hoyt (Box 1874, Folder 3)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Hoyt-Mather (Box 1874, Folder 4)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-McCormick-Merriam (Box 1874, Folder 5)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Myers-Park (Box 1874, Folder 6)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Park-Peters (Box 1874, Folder 7)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Pomeroy-Ramsdell (Box 1874, Folder 8)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Reed-Robinson (Box 1874, Folder 9)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Rowe-Scannell (Box 1874, Folder 10)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Scriber-Sibley (Box 1874, Folder 11)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Swartwout-Smith (Box 1874, Folder 12)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Spencer-Stobie (Box 1874, Folder 13)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Storey-Thayer (Box 1874, Folder 14)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Tierney-Tuttle (Box 1874, Folder 15)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Twyeffort-Wainwright (Box 1874, Folder 16)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Walker-Washburn (Box 1874, Folder 17)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Waterman-Watters (Box 1874, Folder 18)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Whaley-Wood (Box 1874, Folder 19)
  - Class Secretary's Notes-Wood-Yount (Box 1874, Folder 20)
  - Class Secretary's Photo Album (Box 1874.2)
  - Senior Parties, 1915 (Box 1872, Folder 1)
  - Smock Day, 1915 (Box 1872, Folder 2)
  - Sophomore Push Committee, 1913 (Box 1872, Folder 3)
  - Sophomore Reception, 1912 (Box 1872, Folder 4)
  - Songs, undated (Box 1872, Folder 5)
  - Step Sings, 1915 (Box 1872, Folder 6)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1915 (Box 1872, Folder 7)
  - Senior Dramatics: Business Manager's Ledger, 1915 (Box 1872, Folder 8)
  - Senior Dramatics: Photographs, 1915 (Box 1872, Folder 9)
  - Senior Dramatics: Photographs, 1915 (Box 1872, Folder 10)
  - Class Supper, 1915 (Box 1872, Folder 11)
  - Treasurer Account Ledger, 1954-1978 (Box 1872, Folder 12)
  - Individuals A-D (Box 1875)
  - Individuals E-R (Box 1876)
  - Individuals S-Z (Box 1877)
  - Adams, Eva Bryant (memoirs) (Box 1879)
  - Bauer, Dorothea Louise (photo album) (Box 1881.1)
  - Pearce, Katharine Standish (photo album, class notes) (Box 1880)
  - Pearce, Charolotte Crosby (memorabilia book) (Box 1881.2)
  - Rochester, Madeleine Eugenie (memorabilia book) (Box 1881)
  - Sackett, Eleanor Lamont (memorabilia books) (Box 1881.3)
  - Washburn, Helen (Scrapbook) (Box 1881.4)
- Class of 1916 Records, 1912-1996; 23.729 linear feet (27 containers)
  The Class of 1916 was the thirty-seventh entering class and the thirty-seventh graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1916 records, 1912-1996, contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1916, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, pamphlets, and other memorabilia.
  - Baccalaureate, 1916 (Box 1882, Folder 1)
  - Book of Statistics, 1916 (Box 1882, Folder 2)
  - Commencement, 1916 (Box 1882, Folder 3)
  - Commencement Clippings, 1916 (Box 1882, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Music, 1916 (Box 1882, Folder 5)
  - Commencement Photos, 1916 (Box 1882, Folder 6)
  - Commencement Speaker, 1916 (Box 1882, Folder 7)
  - Freshman Frolic, 1912 (Box 1882, Folder 8)
  - Freshman Grind, 1912 (Box 1882, Folder 9)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1912-1913 (Box 1882, Folder 10)
  - Groups, 1912-1916 (Box 1882, Folder 11)
  - Hoop Rolling, 1916 (Box 1882, Folder 12)
  - Ivy Day, 1916 (Box 1882, Folder 13)
  - Ivy Day Photos, 1916 (Box 1882, Folder 14)
  - Junior Frolic, 1915 (Box 1882, Folder 15)
  - Junior Prom, 1915 (Box 1882, Folder 16)
  - Junior Prom: Garden Party, 1915 (Box 1882, Folder 17)
  - Junior Ushers, 1915 (Box 1882, Folder 18)
  - Last Chapel, 1916 (Box 1883, Folder 1)
  - Class Letters, 1916-1970 (Box 1883, Folder 2)
  - Class Letters, 1970-1980 (Box 1883, Folder 3)
  - Organization, 1915-1916 (Box 1883, Folder 4)
  - Reunions-General, 1941 (Box 1884, Folder 1)
  - Reunions, 1917-1919 (Box 1884, Folder 2)
  - Reunions, 1921 (Box 1884, Folder 3)
  - Reunions, 1926 (Box 1884, Folder 4)
  - Reunions, 1931 (Box 1884, Folder 5)
  - Reunions, 1936 (Box 1884, Folder 6)
  - Reunions, 1941 (Box 1884, Folder 7)
  - Reunions-Photographs, 1941 (Box 1884, Folder 8)
  - Reunions-Photographs, 1941 (Box 1884, Folder 9)
  - Reunions, 1946 (Box 1884, Folder 10)
  - Reunions, 1951 (Box 1884, Folder 11)
  - Reunions, 1956 (Box 1884, Folder 12)
  - Reunions, 1961 (Box 1884, Folder 13)
  - Reunions, 1966 (Box 1884, Folder 14)
  - Reunions, 1970 (Box 1884, Folder 15)
  - Reunions, 1971 (Box 1884, Folder 16)
  - Reunions, 1975-1976 (Box 1884, Folder 17)
  - Reunions, 1981 (Box 1884, Folder 18)
  - Reunions, 1986 (Box 1884, Folder 19)
  - Reunions, 1991-1992 (Box 1884, Folder 20)
  - Reunions, 1996 (Box 1884, Folder 21)
  - Reunions, undated (Box 1884, Folder 22)
  - Reunions-Songs, undated (Box 1884, Folder 23)
  - Step Sings, 1915-1916 (Box 1883, Folder 5)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1916 (Box 1883, Folder 6)
  - Senior Dramatics: Photos, 1916 (Box 1883, Folder 7)
  - Senior Dramatics: Photo Album, 1916 (Box 1883, Folder 8)
  - Senior Reception, 1916 (Box 1883, Folder 9)
  - Smock Day, 1916 (Box 1883, Folder 10)
  - Songs, undated (Box 1883, Folder 11)
  - Sophomore Reception, 1913 (Box 1883, Folder 12)
  - Class Supper, 1916 (Box 1883, Folder 13)
  - Class Secretary's Records of Class Members (Box 1883.1)
  - Individuals A-C (Box 1884.1)
  - Individuals D-L (Box 1885)
  - Individuals M-Z (Box 1886)
  - Book of 1916 Class Reunion Attendance (Box 1884.2)
  - Attwill, Dorothy (correspondence) (Box 1887)
  - Attwill, Dorothy (correspondence) (Box 1888)
  - Darr, Marjorie Helen (memorabilia book) (Box 1894.1)
  - Downes, Elizabeth Sargent (photo album) (Box 1894.10)
  - Fessenden, Francis Alida (memorabilia book) (Box 1894.2)
  - Hammer, Mabel White (memorabilia book) (Box 1894.10)
  - Hedlund, Ruth F. (scrapbook) (Box 1894.3)
  - Hedlund, Ruth F. (scrapbook) (Box 1894.4)
  - Hovey, Grace (class notes and reunion) (Box 1889)
  - Hugus, Elizabeth Wood (memorabilia book) (Box 1894.5)
  - Jones, Margaret Norris (photo album, scrapbook) (Box 1890)
  - Patton, Augusta (memorabilia book) (Box 1894.6)
  - Rusk, Elizabeth Katharine (memorabilia book) (Box 1894.7)
  - Schmolze, Mildred Constance (memorabilia book, photo album) (Box 1894.8)
  - Smith, Marjorie B. (class notes) (Box 1891)
  - Smith, Marjorie B. (class notes, diary, photos, misc) (Box 1892)
  - Smith, Marjorie B. (memorabilia book) (Box 1892.1)
  - Stebbins, Eunice Burr (memorabilia book) (Box 1893)
  - Wellman, Marjorie Elizabeth (memorabilia book, photo album) (Box 1894)
  - Wood, Miriam Wealthy (memorabilia book) (Box 1894.9)
- Class of 1917 Records, 1913-1988; 16.646 linear feet (22 containers)
  The Class of 1917 was the thirty-ninth graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1917 records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1917, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, pamphlets, and other memorabilia.
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1917 (Box 1896, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, 1917 (Box 1896, Folder 2)
  - Commencement, 1917 (Box 1896, Folder 3)
  - Commencement Music, 1917 (Box 1896, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Photographs, 1917 (Box 1896, Folder 5)
  - Freshman Frolic, 1913 (Box 1896, Folder 6)
  - Freshman Grind, 1913 (Box 1896, Folder 7)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1913-1914 (Box 1896, Folder 8)
  - Groups, 1914-1917 (Box 1896, Folder 9)
  - Ivy Day, 1917 (Box 1896, Folder 10)
  - Ivy Day Photographs, 1917 (Box 1896, Folder 11)
  - Junior Frolic, 1916 (Box 1896, Folder 12)
  - Junior Prom, 1916 (Box 1896, Folder 13)
  - Junior Ushers, 1916 (Box 1896, Folder 14)
  - Class Letters, 1965-1988 (Box 1896, Folder 15)
  - Organization, 1915-1917 (Box 1896, Folder 16)
  - Reunions, 1922 (Box 1896, Folder 17)
  - Reunions, 1927 (Box 1896, Folder 18)
  - Reunions, 1932 (Box 1896, Folder 19)
  - Reunions, 1937 (Box 1896, Folder 20)
  - Reunions, 1942 (Box 1896, Folder 21)
  - Reunions, 1942 (Box 1896, Folder 22)
  - Reunions, 1947 (Box 1896, Folder 23)
  - Reunions, 1948 (Box 1896, Folder 24)
  - Reunions, 1952 (Box 1896, Folder 25)
  - Reunions, 1957 (Box 1897, Folder 1)
  - Reunions, 1962 (Box 1897, Folder 2)
  - Reunions, 1967 (Box 1897, Folder 3)
  - Reunion Questionnaire: A-C, 1967 (Box 1897, Folder 4)
  - Reunion Questionnaire: D-G, 1967 (Box 1897, Folder 5)
  - Reunion Questionnaire: H-M, 1967 (Box 1897, Folder 6)
  - Reunion Questionnaire: N-S, 1967 (Box 1897, Folder 7)
  - Reunion Questionnaire: T-Y, 1967 (Box 1897, Folder 8)
  - Reunions, 1972 (Box 1897, Folder 9)
  - Reunions, 1977-1982 (Box 1897, Folder 10)
  - Reunions, 1987 (Box 1897, Folder 11)
  - Reunion Songs, undated (Box 1897, Folder 12)
  - Reunion Signature Book, 1918-1987 (Box 1895, Folder 1)
  - Reunion Oversized Group Photo, undated (Box 1895, Folder 2)
  - Secretary's Records, 1913-1915 (Box 1897, Folder 13)
  - Secretary's Records, 1915-1917 (Box 1897, Folder 14)
  - Secretary's Records, 1918-1982 (Box 1897, Folder 15)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1917 (Box 1897, Folder 16)
  - Senior Dramatics-Photographs, 1917 (Box 1897, Folder 17)
  - Sophomore Reception, 1915 (Box 1897, Folder 18)
  - Songs, undated (Box 1897, Folder 19)
  - Step Sings, 1917 (Box 1897, Folder 20)
  - Class Supper, 1917 (Box 1897, Folder 21)
  - Individuals A-G (Box 1898)
  - Individuals H-Lee (Box 1899)
  - Individuals Lewis-Th (Box 1900)
  - Individuals To-Z (Box 1901)
  - Abrams, Stella (Box 1902)
  - Alling, Margaret (photo album) (Box 1906.9)
  - Gibson, Frances Hastings (memorabilia book) (Box 1906.1)
  - Herrick, Marjory (photo album) (Box 1906.9)
  - Kolransch, Marion (photo album) (Box 1906.10)
  - Nottingham, Edith (memorabilia book and photo album) (Box 1906.3)
  - Paine, Margaret Woolson (memorabilia book) (Box 1906.5)
  - Root, Marjorie Stafford (correspondence) (Box 1903)
  - Slaughter, Helen C. (memorabilia book) (Box 1904)
  - Thayer, Mary Harrison (photo album, memorabilia book) (Box 1906.6)
  - Walsh, Florence (memorablilia book) (Box 1905.1)
  - Walsh, Florence Gertrude (memorabilia book) (Box 1906.7)
  - Warner, Harriet L. (photo albums) (Box 1906.10)
  - Wells, Elizabeth (memorabilia book) (Box 1906.8)
  - Wood, Constance Hastings (memorabilia book) (Box 1905)
  - Wood, Constance Hastings (memorabilia book) (Box 1905.1)
  - Yereance, Anita Louise (memorabilia book) (Box 1906)
  - Nute, Grace T. (scrapbook) (Box 1906.4)
- Class of 1918 Records, 1914-1988; 15.375 linear feet (26 containers)
  The Class of 1918 was the fortieth graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1918 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1918, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, treasury information, pamphlets, and other memorabilia.
  - Commencement, 1918 (Box 1907, Folder 1)
  - Commencement-Carmen Saeculare of Horace, 1918 (Box 1907, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Music, 1918 (Box 1907, Folder 3)
  - Commencement Photographs, 1918 (Box 1907, Folder 4)
  - Dues Ledger, 1953-1983 (Box 1907, Folder 5)
  - Freshman Frolic, 1914 (Box 1907, Folder 6)
  - Freshman Grind, 1914 (Box 1907, Folder 7)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1914-1915 (Box 1907, Folder 8)
  - Freshman Party, 1914 (Box 1907, Folder 9)
  - Groups, 1914-1918 (Box 1907, Folder 10)
  - Ivy Day, 1918 (Box 1907, Folder 11)
  - Junior Frolic, 1917 (Box 1907, Folder 12)
  - Junior Prom, 1917 (Box 1907, Folder 13)
  - Class Letters, 1926-1978 (Box 1907, Folder 14)
  - Class Letters, 1926-1977 (Box 1907, Folder 15)
  - Memorials, 1978 (Box 1907, Folder 16)
  - Organization, 1916-1917 (Box 1907, Folder 17)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 1907, Folder 18)
  - Class President's Notebook, 1914-1918 (Box 1907, Folder 19)
  - Reunions, 1918-1922 (Box 1908, Folder 1)
  - Reunions-Photographs, 1922 (Box 1908, Folder 2)
  - Reunions, 1923 (Box 1908, Folder 3)
  - Reunions, 1928 (Box 1908, Folder 4)
  - Reunions, 1933 (Box 1908, Folder 5)
  - Reunions, 1938 (Box 1908, Folder 6)
  - Reunions, 1948 (Box 1908, Folder 7)
  - Reunions, 1953 (Box 1908, Folder 8)
  - Reunions, 1958 (Box 1908, Folder 9)
  - Reunions, 1963 (Box 1908, Folder 10)
  - Reunions, 1968 (Box 1908, Folder 11)
  - Reunions, 1973-1975 (Box 1908, Folder 12)
  - Reunions, 1978 (Box 1908, Folder 13)
  - Reunions, 1988 (Box 1908, Folder 14)
  - Class scrapbooks (Box 1908.2)
  - Seal, Emblem, Animal, etc., undated (Box 1908.1, Folder 1)
  - Secretary's Card Files (Box 1908.4)
  - Secretary's Card Files (Box 1908.5)
  - Secretary's Scrapbooks (Box 1908.3)
  - Class Secretary's Correspondence, 1984-1988 (Box 1908.1, Folder 2)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1918 (Box 1908.1, Folder 3)
  - Songs, undated (Box 1908.1, Folder 4)
  - Sophomore Carnival, 1916 (Box 1908.1, Folder 5)
  - Sophomore Reception, 1916 (Box 1908.1, Folder 6)
  - Class Supper, 1918 (Box 1908.1, Folder 7)
  - Class Tax, 1906-1966 (Box 1908.1, Folder 8)
  - Class Treasurer, 1964-1981 (Box 1908.1, Folder 9)
  - Treasurer's Correspondence, 1945-1966 (Box 1908.1, Folder 10)
  - Treasurer's Account Ledger, 1915-1972 (Box 1908.1, Folder 11)
  - Treasurer's Account Ledger, 1973-1983 (Box 1908.1, Folder 12)
  - Individuals A-E (Box 1909)
  - Individuals F-H (Box 1910)
  - Individuals I-K (Box 1911)
  - Individuals L-S (Box 1912)
  - Individuals T-Z (Box 1913)
  - Arey, Helen Winnifred (scrapbook) (Box 1913.1)
  - Babcock, Dorothy Muriel (memorabilia books) (Box 1918.1)
  - de Schweinitz, Louise (diaries and class notes) (Box 1914)
  - de Schweinitz, Louise (memorabilia book) (Box 1914.1)
  - de Schweinitz, Louise (memorabilia book) (Box 1914.4)
  - Fain, Dorothy (scrapbook) (Box 1914.3)
  - Fain, Dorothy (photo album) (Box 1914.2)
  - Fessenden, Anna Parker (memorabilia book) (Box 1918.2)
  - Harrison, Dorothea Katharine (memorabilia book) (Box 1914.4)
  - Hepburn, Margaret (Box 1910.1)
  - Kendrick, Doris (memorabilia book) (Box 1915)
  - Knight, Dorothy Hamet (memorabilia book) (Box 1918.2)
  - Root, Donna Louise (memorabilia book) (Box 1918.3)
  - Roth, Emma Dietze (photo album) (Box 1915)
  - Rothberg, Vera Estelle (correspondence) (Box 1917)
  - Rothberg, Vera Estelle (correspondence) (Box 1918)
  - Scoville, Magdalene Frances (memorabilia book, photo album) (Box 1918.4)
  - Witte, Helen Frances (memorabilia book) (Box 1918.5)
- Class of 1919 Records, 1915-1997; 18.271 linear feet (24 containers)
  The Class of 1919 was the forty-first graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1919 records contains materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1919, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, newsletters, pamphlets, and other memorabilia.
  - Alumnae Council, 1970 (Box 1919, Folder 1)
  - Commencement, 1919 (Box 1919, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Address, 1919 (Box 1919, Folder 3)
  - Commencement Music, 1919 (Box 1919, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Photographs, 1919 (Box 1919, Folder 5)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1915 (Box 1919, Folder 6)
  - Freshman Grind, 1915 (Box 1919, Folder 7)
  - Groups, 1915-1919 (Box 1919, Folder 8)
  - Hoop Rolling, 1919 (Box 1919, Folder 9)
  - Ivy Day, 1919 (Box 1919, Folder 10)
  - Ivy Day-Photographs, 1919 (Box 1919, Folder 11)
  - Junior Carnival, 1918 (Box 1919, Folder 12)
  - Class Letters ("Boojum"), 1920-1960 (Box 1919, Folder 13)
  - Class Letters ("Boojum"), 1961-1989 (Box 1919, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous, 1916-1935 (Box 1919, Folder 15)
  - Organization, 1915-1917; 1989-1997 (Box 1919, Folder 16)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1919 (Box 1919, Folder 17)
  - Reunions, 1924 (Box 1920, Folder 1)
  - Reunions, 1929 (Box 1920, Folder 2)
  - Reunions, 1934 (Box 1920, Folder 3)
  - Reunions, 1939 (Box 1920, Folder 4)
  - Reunions, 1944 (Box 1920, Folder 5)
  - Reunions, 1949 (Box 1920, Folder 6)
  - Reunions, 1954 (Box 1920, Folder 7)
  - Reunions, 1959 (Box 1920, Folder 8)
  - Reunions, 1964 (Box 1920, Folder 9)
  - Reunions, 1969 (Box 1920, Folder 10)
  - Reunions, 1974 (Box 1920, Folder 11)
  - Reunions, 1979 (Box 1920, Folder 12)
  - Reunions, 1984 (Box 1920, Folder 13)
  - Reunions, 1989 (Box 1920, Folder 14)
  - Reunions, 1994 (Box 1920, Folder 15)
  - Reunion Memorabilia (Box 1920.1)
  - Reunion Photo (Box 1920.5)
  - Class Secretary's Card File (Box 1920.2)
  - Class Secretary's Card File (Box 1920.3)
  - Class Secretary's Card File (Box 1920.4)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1919 (Box 1919, Folder 18)
  - Senior Dramatics-Business Manager's Report, 1919 (Box 1919, Folder 19)
  - Senior Dramatics-Miscellaneous, 1919 (Box 1919.1, Folder 1)
  - Senior Dramatics-Photographs, 1919 (Box 1919.1, Folder 2)
  - Senior Dramatics-The Yellow Jacket (text), 1919 (Box 1919.1, Folder 3)
  - Class Songs, undated (Box 1919.1, Folder 4)
  - Sophomore Reception, 1917 (Box 1919.1, Folder 5)
  - Step Sings, 1919 (Box 1919.1, Folder 6)
  - Class Supper, 1919 (Box 1919.1, Folder 7)
  - Individuals A-B (Box 1921)
  - Individuals C-K (Box 1921.1)
  - Individuals L-Z (Box 1922)
  - Ames, Doris Bingham (memorabilia book) (Box 1927.1)
  - Atwater, Henrietta (memorabilia book) (Box 1927.2)
  - Bedell, Eleanor Crehore (correspondence, financial) (Box 1924)
  - Burke, Grace M. (photo album) (Box 1924.1)
  - Clarke, Edith (scrapbook) (Box 1924.2)
  - Cohen, Helen Rose (class notes) (Box 1925)
  - Cohen, Helen Rose (memorabilia book) (Box 1925.1)
  - Coit, Edith Neafie (correspondence, diary, photographs) (Box 1926)
  - Davis, Helen Edna (scrapbooks) (Box 1927.3)
  - Decker, Bernice (photo album) (Box 1927.3)
  - Ely, Martha Weare (course materials from Cambridge School of Architecture, Class notebooks) (Box 1927)
  - Fessenden, Florence Ethelda (memorabilia book) (Box 1927.6)
  - Graffte, Marjorie (Box 1927.9)
  - Hooper, Marjorie R. (scrapbook) (Box 1927.7)
  - Shea, Mary (memorabilia album) (Box 1927.5)
  - Staunton, Florence (photo album) (Box 1924.1)
  - Thomas, Dorothea (memorabilia book) (Box 1927.6)
  - Winchester, Margaret (scrapbook) (Box 1927.8, Box 1927.10)
- Class of 1920 Records, 1916-1965; 13.833 linear feet (19 containers)
  The Class of 1920 was the forty-second graduating class of Smith College.